okay so once it creates everything it's gonna tell me a few details so it tells me other things that
i still need that are required fields and then it will give me a preview link so let's have it fill
out the practical details this is just a test so could you please just create content for the
practical details and any other missing information just so that all of the fields
are filled out thank you the nice thing is so especially with seo creating like every picture
you put up and every video it needs to have alt text so that seo can know what is in that picture
for search engines and the really nice thing is that doing it this way chat gpg just creates all
of that for you so the actual excuse it the slight nudity having a little fun with the uh
creator so you know as much as you probably would want to really carefully look over the
story section details the other aspects like the seo title and the seo description
so yeah
little copy buttons just in case i wanted to copy it paste it back into chat gpt with edits
we'll hide that just to see the whole thing and then all we have to do is hit publish
cannot publish dimensions are required so we're going to close this and we'll just tell chat gpt
it says that it still needs the dimensions if you could just make something up um even though
it's not totally applicable these are required fields for it to be able to publish because of the
type of product that will normally be on the website so you can just make something up for now
and then everything else looks good so you can publish it right after you add those fields
thank you done nice and it's published now
you